Oleksandr Haimanov React Native & React Expert

E-mail: ninjak0324@gmail.com

Address: Valentinovskaya, Kharkiv, Ukraine

SUMMARY

I am a Senior Web & Mobile App Developer with 5 years experience. My top skill is Javascript (ES6) and Javascript Frameworks like React Native, React / Redux (Mobx), Angular and Node. And I have rich experience with Laravel, Django and MySQL.

I promise pixel perfect design. Thanks for your time.

SKILLS

- HTML/HTML5, CSS/CSS3
- Javascript (ES6), React Native, React/Redux (Mobx), Angular, Vue, Node, Bootstrap, jQuery
- PHP, Laravel
- Python, Django
- MySQL, MongoDB
- Version Control System (VCS): Git, GitHub

EDUCATION

National Aerospace University 'Kharkiv Aviation Institute'

(2012 - 2016)

Bachelor of Engineering (B.Eng.), Computer engineering

EXPERIENCE

Senior Web & Mobile App Developer - Freelance (2018.9 - Recent)

Web & Mobile App Developer - G-Plans

(2017.12 - 2018.8)

React Native / Mobx, Django

https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/g-plans-nutrition/id1287437272?mt=8

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.gplans &hl=en US

Angular5, Django

https://g-plans.com

Front-end Developer - Nextiva

(2015.3 - 2017.10)

Angular2, Laravel

https://www.channelmum.com

React Native / Redux

https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/hud-1-hookup-app/id1042814349?mt=8